isoc.ae 2017-02-16

# Privacy Policy

**Collection of Information**

IEG training center does not collect personally identifying data, such as names, addresses, email addresses, and the like, except when voluntarily submitted by web site visitors.

For non-registered users, IEG Institute does not collect personally identifying data from site visitors. For registered users, we only collect personally identifiable information which you provide. This information is normally provided when you (a) register as a user of the site; (b) send us email or (c) choose to receive emails from IEG Institute.

The personally identifiable information which you provide is used only to customize the content and advertising which you see, and for us to contact you by email when you have authorized us to do so.

Non-personally identifiable information is used anonymously and in the aggregate for us to conduct research and to improve the performance and compatibility of our services. This information includes technical information such as browser type, computer platform, as well as click-stream information, searches performed and other website activities which we record and analyze in the aggregate.

 **All Credit/Debit cards’ details or information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third parties.**

 **Collection of Information by Third Parties**

At this time either IEG training center or its affiliates is involved in the charging and processing of credit card information when you make a purchase. Purchases are processed by PayPal, neither of which share your credit card information with IEG Institute.

 **Disclosure of Information**

IEG training center will not disclose or share any personal information you provide to us with any
